IREM HARNAK

FRONT END DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+1 647 994 5645



irem@iremharnak.com



iremharnak.com



Iremharnak

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- HTML, CSS, JS
- React
- Git, Bitbucket, JIRA
- Express
- Python
- Mongo, Mongoose
- Django
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma, Sketch, Invision

EDUCATION

Certificate - 2022

Software Engineering Immersive General Assembly

Diploma - 2020

Interaction Design & Development George Brown College

Master's - 2002

European Cultural Policy & Management
University of Warwick

PROFILE

I am a front end developer with a background in user experience design. My coding journey began with building interactive and engaging experiences in VR/AR. From there I began experimenting with the web, and fell in love with development. I have a passion for building applications and working collaboratively in a team to make the best possible product.

PROJECTS

CASECOUNT (MERN STACK- GROUP PROJECT)

- Created an online smart phone case customizing store offering a wide range of phones. As a user you can select your colour, patterns as well as randomize them to your liking.
- Used React, Express, MongoDB, JWT, NodeJS, React-Bootstrap & CSS, Figma
- Implemented Stripe API to mimic a checkout experience.

MAJOR (E-COMMERCE WEBSITE— SOLO PROJECT)

- Created an full crud e-commerce website where you can shop for sneakers
- Used NodeJS, Express, MongoDB, Mongoose, OAuth Authentication, CSS

SIMON (BROWSER GAME— SOLO PROJECT)

- Created the retro Simon game where user reproduces the sound they hear on the UII
- Used HTML, CSS, JS, Figma

TINTEREST (BROWSER GAME— GROUP PROJECT)

- Created an image sharing social app much like Pinterest
- Used Python, Django, PostgreSQL, RESTful APIs, Amazon S3, JS, CSS, Materialize, HTML

WORK EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT DESIGNER

BMO | November 2021- Current

- Working with PO's, BA's, devs, researchers, QA's and other stakeholders to deliver a modern investment platform.
- Creating various web responsive prototypes (mobile, web, tablet, mobile native)
- Working closely with developers to build a seamless user experience and interactions
- Shadowing UI devs occasionally with front end tasks and misc bug fixes

IREM HARNAK

FRONT END DEVELOPER

SKILLS

PROFESSIONAL

- Attention to detail
- Critical thinking
- Communication
- Resourcefulness
- Adaptability
- Time management
- Problem solving

EXTRA

VENICE VR IN COMPETITION

Linear Storytelling / 2018

INTERESTS

- Al
- Machine Learning
- Storytelling
- Languages
- Fitness
- AR/VR
- Visual Arts

WORK EXPERIENCE CONTINUED

UI/UX DESIGNER

Dark Slope/Lumeto | January 2021- November 2021

- Worked with the product owner & rest of the team to deliver a coherent project vision. Connected with users to identify & validate pain points.
- Collaborated with developers to explore new capabilities, assess constraints & feasibility.
- Crafted & presented design directions & specifications that support an iterative development & prototyping.

AR CREATOR RESIDENT

Snap Inc | October 2020 - November 2020

- Designed an AR experience to be used as a Snapchat Lens based on a motivational app concept.
- Collaborated with a creative director/designer & Snap developers to implement effective storytelling & user engagement.
- Designed interaction flows & various mockups to convey the vision.
- Created 3D assets, used VR tools and Javascript to rig animation.
- Combined animations and custom ML in Lens Studio to create the storytelling lens.

PRODUCT DESIGNER

Cream Productions | May 2020- August 2020

- Designed and delivered a coherent vision & a playable prototype for a casual game in VR.
- Helped build strategy & positioning for the game by doing user interviews, creating personas and delivering a competitive & landscape analysis.
- Designed the game storyline & levels in collaboration with my team.
- Generated user stories, wireframes to convey & implement ideas.

UX DESIGNER / UX RESEARCHER

GBC Office of Research & Innovation | November 2018 - April 2020

- Worked with companies such as Autodesk, EcoSpex, RainGrid on different stages of their product cycle.
- Identified core functional requirements and formulated design suggestions by doing heuristics evaluations, user research and task analysis.
- Generated system maps, personas, user journeys and information architecture for design proposals.
- Developed wireframes, interactive prototypes for mobile, tablet and web.